Guide to the McCann-Erickson Audiovisual Collection, 1980s-1990s and undated RL.00863
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Original Videotapes, 1980s-1990s, 49 boxes
  - 452. Colchones Shelter; Selsum Shampoo. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 1:00
    - Selsun shampoo: Beauty Parlor (Mexico) (Box 30)
  - 453. Argentina--Youth Oriented Commercials. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Wagon Wheels cookies: Cookies in Bed (Box 30)
    - Foster sunglasses: Red Jacket (Box 30)
    - Levi's: Launderette (Box 30)
    - Levi's: Bath (Box 30)
    - Plymouth Duster: Punk Music (Box 30)
    - Chrysler Laser: Futurist City (Box 30)
    - Red Beer: Greyhounds (Box 30)
    - Coke: Cool Moves (Box 30)
    - Coke: Hard Rock (Box 30)
    - L'Oreal Studio: Video Screens (USA) (Box 30)
    - L'Oreal Studio: Band (French) (Box 30)
  - 454. Australian Commercials, Tape 1. Undated. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 60:00
    - Holeproof (Box 30)
    - Lotto: Sports (Box 30)
    - Honda bikes (Box 30)
    - Holeproof (Box 30)
    - Hoover washer/dryer (Box 30)
    - Patons (Box 30)
    - 2 Day FM (Box 30)
    - Wranglers: Roller Skates (Box 30)
    - Katrin (Box 30)
    - Thai training (Box 30)
    - Sussans (Box 30)
    - Reader's Digest: Kremlin (Box 30)
    - KB neighborhood (Box 30)
    - Saab Turbo: Outback (Box 30)
    - Vidal Sasson (Box 30)
    - Hall's Carpets: Carpet Tea (Box 30)
    - Hall's Carpets: Carpeters (Box 30)
    - McLeary Brothers Carpets (5x) (Box 30)
    - Lottery (Box 30)
    - Bluegrass Jeans (Box 30)
    - Heinz Vegetable Soup (Box 30)
    - Chatelle Napoleon brandy (Box 30)
    - Pink Floyd: The Wall (Box 30)
    - Crunch & Munch dog food (Box 30)
    - Bornhoffer bread (Box 30)
    - Lotto: Station (Box 30)
    - Moove island (Box 30)
    - Operation Noah (Box 30)
    - Break Down the Barriers (Box 30)
    - Self-Help (Box 30)
    - Cadbury Chocolate Éclair Pops (Box 30)
    - Tia Maria: Piano (Box 30)
    - Gas: Sydney (Box 30)
    - The Age (Box 30)
    - Vision saucepan (Box 30)
    - BP: Solar Car (Box 30)
    - King G. (Box 30)
    - NSW Art Gallery (Box 30)
    - Apple Computer: Kids (Box 30)
    - Mastercard (Box 30)
    - State Wide Building Society (Box 30)
    - State Bank: Home (Box 30)
    - State Bank: Home Extension (Box 30)
    - State Bank: Business (Box 30)
    - Lotto: Chinese Restaurant (Box 30)
    - Sigma chains (Box 30)
    - Tia Maria: Stripe (Box 30)
    - Test Cricket B&H (Box 30)
    - Holden Commodore (Box 30)
    - Gillette Blue II (Box 30)
    - Toppleless Tray (Box 30)
    - BMW (Box 30)
    - Reach (Box 30)
    - Smith's Crisps (Box 30)
    - Twisties (Box 30)
    - Sequel Computer: Paper Pile (Box 30)
    - Morten: Homestead (Box 30)
    - Samboy Chips (2x) (Box 30)
    - State Wide Building Society (2x) (Box 30)
    - Hoover washer/dryer (3x) (Box 30)
    - Department of Transport (3x) (Box 30)
    - Corningware (Box 30)
    - Duralex glasses (Box 30)
    - John West tuna (Box 30)
    - South Australian Front: Drink and Drive (Box 30)
    - Farmers' Union Milk: Punk (Box 30)
    - Dorf (Box 30)
    - Tetley Tea (Box 30)
    - MGM (Box 30)
    - IBM: Timber Yard (Box 30)
    - Optical City (Box 30)
  - 455. Australian Commercials, Tape 2. Undated. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 60:00
    - Fun Factory (Box 30)
    - Sports Girl (Box 30)
    - Holeproof: No Nickers (Box 30)
    - Scotowels: Drink (Box 30)
    - NSW Cancer Council (Box 30)
    - N.Z. Insurance (Box 30)
    - Ryvita (Box 30)
    - State Bank: Visa (Box 30)
    - Royal Blind Society (Box 30)
    - Glad Handle Tie Bags (Box 30)
    - Bamp;H World Series Cup (Box 30)
    - Ski Yogurt (Box 30)
    - Winners at Work (Box 30)
    - Toyota Hi Lux: Country (Box 30)
    - Volvo (Box 30)
    - Mobil: Gas to Gasoline (Box 30)
    - Mobil 1: Rally Formula (Box 30)
    - Olympic: Aussie Tough (Box 30)
    - Keiser Stuhl: Rose (Box 30)
    - Campari (Box 30)
    - Just Juice: New Zealand (Box 30)
    - Moccona (Box 30)
    - Coca-Cola: Beach Can (Box 30)
    - Check Heaton: Click Clack Wool (Box 30)
    - Sexy Legs (Box 30)
    - BP: Resources (Box 30)
    - BP: Sponsorship (Box 30)
    - Toyota: Road Safety (Box 30)
    - Aquasun sunscreen (Box 30)
    - Australis (Box 30)
    - Scholl Sneaker Treater (Box 30)
    - Kit Kat: Autobank (Box 30)
    - Plaistow cooking chocolate (Box 30)
    - Birdseye fish fillets (Box 30)
    - Vegemite (Box 30)
    - Electrolux vacuum cleaner (Box 30)
    - Stratco fencing (Box 30)
    - Glad foil (Box 30)
    - Scott Towels (Box 30)
    - Ronson shaver (Box 30)
    - Replay erasable pen (Box 30)
    - NSW Lottery (Box 30)
    - Ansett: 200-People Boeing 767 (Box 30)
    - Canada: Donald Sutherland (Box 30)
    - Thai Airlines (Box 30)
    - Australia Post (Box 30)
    - Portman's t-shirts (Box 30)
    - Lovely Pancakes (Box 30)
    - Statewide Building Society (Box 30)
    - Cobb & Co. (3x) (Box 30)
    - Adelaide Central Mission (Box 30)
    - Supertext subtitles (Box 30)
    - Hotham Building Society (Box 30)
    - Birdseye corn (Box 30)
    - Kleenex VIP Nappies (Box 30)
    - National Bank: New Zealand (Box 30)
    - Carlton brewers (Box 30)
    - J&B (Box 30)
    - Rheem (Box 30)
    - Victa (Box 30)
    - Cradle Valley Cheese (Box 30)
    - Palings (Box 30)
    - Poleconomy (Box 30)
    - Olin Chemicals (Box 30)
    - McWilliams Wines (Box 30)
    - Volvo (Box 30)
    - Birdseye crisps (Box 30)
    - Save the Children (Box 30)
    - Breville Kitchen Wizz (Box 30)
    - 2VE: Clint Eastwood (Box 30)
    - Pine O Clean (Box 30)
    - Campari (Box 30)
    - Pine O Clean: Germ House (Box 30)
    - Birdseye Range (Box 30)
    - Gravon (Box 30)
    - Harper's Bazaar (Box 30)
    - Twistos (Box 30)
    - Holeproof (Box 30)
    - IBM: Wangaratta (Box 30)
    - Samboy (Box 30)
    - AGC (Box 30)
    - Tarasc Black Label (Box 30)
    - Apple Macintosh (Box 30)
    - Nestlé Tea Sling (Box 30)
    - Esanda Finance (Box 30)
    - Bushell's Master Roast Coffee (Box 30)
    - Thai Airlines (Box 30)
    - Ansett Club (Box 30)
  - 456. TV Interviews: Interview with Barry Day (Australia). 1984. Umatic. TRT: 4:15 (Box 30)
  - 457. Black and Decker (Brazil). 1985. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    [Brand transition in combining G.E. home appliance line and Black & Decker line in the Brazilian market. Research results are discussed.]
    - Black & Decker: A Great Brand (Box 30)
    - Black & Decker: A Great Brand (Box 30)
    - GE sponsor call-out (Box 30)
    - GE teaser (Box 30)
    - Black & Decker sponsor call-out (Box 30)
    - Black & Decker: A Great Brand (Box 30)
    - GE/B&D: The Joining (Box 30)
  - 458. The British Connection: D.L. Taffner Limited--Thames. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 30)
    [Alastair Burnett hosts a presentation of the continuing role, influence, and impact of the British in the United States: even over 200 years after the U.S. declared independence. Areas discussed include government, business, banking, law, education, art, culture, television, media, movies, industry, technology, fashion, artists, music, advertising (interview with Barry Day), royalty, and politics.]
  - 459. McCann-Erickson Advertising of Canada Ltd--Presentation Reel. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Christie Calais: Billboard (Box 30)
    - Coke: Launch/Walk (Box 30)
    - Kodak: Imagination (Box 30)
    - Oreo: Moreo (Box 30)
    - Diet Sprite: Skyline (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Systems (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Newlyweds (Box 30)
    - Minute Maid: Whoosh (Box 30)
    - Century 21: Confidence (Box 30)
    - Canadian Canners: Dis-A-Spearing (Box 30)
    - Tetley Tea: Time and Motion (Box 30)
    - Christie Brown: Chip Biters (Box 30)
    - Gelco: Taxi (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Mobelfakta (Box 30)
  - 460. McCann Demo 8x30--Vancouver Work Only (B.C., Century 21, IKEA). 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - B.C. Dairy: Clock (Box 30)
    - B.C. Dairy: Studio (Box 30)
    - Century 21: Power to Move/Lifting House (Box 30)
    - B.C. Packer/Cloverleaf Tuna: Luck (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Newlyweds (Box 30)
    - Ikea: System (French) (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Sophisticate (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Mobelfakta (Box 30)
  - 461IKEA Canada. 1987. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Ikea: System (French) (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Newlyweds (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Sophisticate (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Mobelfakta (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Nightmare (Box 30)
    - Ikea: G-Men (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Day Off (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Shadow (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Ingemar/Edmonton Opening (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Ingemar/Edmonton Opening (Box 30)
    - Ikea: Ingemar/Edmonton Opening (Box 30)
  - 462. Heinz-Ufe Wonderland (Cantonese). 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 31)
    - Rice & Hi-Pro: Wonderland (Cantonese) (Box 31)
  - 463. Jose Antonio Camacho (Chile). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Banco de Chile: Telaraña (Box 31)
    - Banco de Chile: Cajas (Box 31)
    - Banco de Chile: Cajero Automático (Box 31)
    - Banco de Chile: Trillizos (Box 31)
    - Dos en Uno: Tiffanys (candy) (Box 31)
    - Nestlé: Manjar Nestlé (Box 31)
    - C.T.C.: Chile (Box 31)
    - Chilectra: Cantado Bajo La Lluvia (Box 31)
  - 464. Lee Cooper Cinema: Le Rythme. 1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Lee Cooper: Le Rythme (Box 31)
  - 465. Cannes: Catalogue, Newlyweds, Systems. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Kodak: Imagination (Box 31)
    - Ikea: Catalogue (Box 31)
    - Ikea: Newlyweds (Box 31)
    - Ikea: Systems (Box 31)
  - 466. Bonne Fournee (Paris Office). 1986. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 1:00
    - Bonne Fournée (Box 31)
  - 467. 10 Ans de Cinema et de television Publicitaires (1 eme partie). Undated. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown.
    - Harpic (Box 31)
    - Sauter (Box 31)
    - La Maison de Marie-Claire (Box 31)
    - Mobilier de France (Box 31)
    - Lesieur (Baxil) (Box 31)
    - Gervais Danone (Floréal) (Box 31)
    - Maggi (Box 31)
    - 3M France (Scotch Magic) (Box 31)
    - Samos (Box 31)
    - Fromageries Bel (Kiri) (Box 31)
    - Vapona (Box 31)
    - Materna (Box 31)
    - Renault 4 (Box 31)
    - Christophle (Box 31)
    - Le Bon Marché (Box 31)
    - Sopad-Picorette (Box 31)
    - Uniroyal (Box 31)
    - BSN-Canada Dry (Box 31)
    - Fromageries Bel (La Vache Qui Rit) (Box 31)
    - S.N.C.F. (Box 31)
    - Assurances-Vie (Box 31)
    - Poulets Douce France (Box 31)
    - S.N.C.F. (Box 31)
    - Cadbury Fry France (Finger) (Box 31)
    - Fly-Tox (Box 31)
    - Stemm (Box 31)
    - Minnesota 3M (Scotch Magic) (Box 31)
    - Air Wick (Box 31)
    - S.N.C.F. (Box 31)
    - Fromageries Bel (Aperit-Cube) (Box 31)
    - Dim (Box 31)
    - Dim (Box 31)
    - Singer (Box 31)
    - Sopalin (Kleenex) (Box 31)
    - Winston (Box 31)
    - Dargaud (Pilote) (Box 31)
    - Sopalin (Kleenex) (Box 31)
    - Manufrance (Box 31)
    - Wrangler (Box 31)
    - Canada Dry (Box 31)
    - Sopalin (Kleenex) (Box 31)
    - Loterie Nationale (Box 31)
    - Pingouin (Box 31)
    - Union Carbide (Glad) (Box 31)
    - Ciby Geigy (Air Wick) (Box 31)
    - Tournus (Box 31)
    - Sauter (Box 31)
    - Crédit Fonciers de France (Box 31)
    - Stemm (Box 31)
    - La Pie Qui Chante (Michoko) (Box 31)
    - Mutzig (Box 31)
    - Leyland (Princess) (Box 31)
    - Sarlino (Novilon) (Box 31)
    - Rodier (Box 31)
    - Rank Xerox (Box 31)
    - Samsonite (Box 31)
    - Peugeot 104 (Box 31)
    - Agfa Gevaert (Pocket Agfamatic) (Box 31)
    - Sopad (Fondant Dessert) (Box 31)
    - Schweppes Bitter Lemon (Box 31)
    - Lesieur (Box 31)
    - Pentel Ball (Box 31)
    - Urgo (Box 31)
    - Citroën (Box 31)
    - Benckiser (Calgon) (Box 31)
    - Pentel Ball (Box 31)
    - Comité Français d'Education Pour La Santé (Box 31)
    - Mapa (Box 31)
    - Comité Français d'Education Pour La Santé (Box 31)
    - P.T.T. (Box 31)
    - Comité Français d'Education Pour La Santé (Box 31)
    - Gloria (Croquettes en Sauce) (Box 31)
    - Lacoste (Box 31)
    - Yves St.-Laurent Parfums (Rive Gauche) (Box 31)
    - Vittel (Box 31)
    - Agence Pour Les Économies d'Énergie (Box 31)
    - Findus (Box 31)
    - Quaker (Fido Chat) (Box 31)
    - 3M (Scotch Magic) (Box 31)
    - Samsonite (Box 31)
    - Renault 5 (Box 31)
    - Lesieur (Mir) (Box 31)
    - Darty (Box 31)
    - Lotus (Box 31)
    - Rowntree McKintosh (Quality Street) (Box 31)
    - Green Sands (Box 31)
    - Rank Xerox (Box 31)
    - BSN-Canada Dry (Box 31)
    - BIC (Box 31)
    - Kelton (Box 31)
    - Belin (Crackers) (Box 31)
    - Agence Nationale Pour l'Emploi (Box 31)
    - Schweppes (Box 31)
    - Eram (Box 31)
    - Saupiquet (Box 31)
    - Colgate (Gama) (Box 31)
    - Laboratoire Roger Bellon (Solutricine) (Box 31)
    - Banania (Box 31)
    - Biscuiterie Nantaise (BN) (Box 31)
    - Banania (Box 31)
    - Johnson Française (Pliz) (Box 31)
    - Sopad (Maggi) (Box 31)
    - Elida Gibbs (Très Très Très) (Box 31)
    - Ministère de l'Intérieur (Box 31)
    - Elida Gibbs (Très Très Très) (Box 31)
    - Éminence (Box 31)
    - Elida Gibbs (Très Très Très) (Box 31)
    - Bureau de Vérification de la Publicité (Box 31)
    - Renault 4 (Box 31)
    - Hippopotamus (Box 31)
    - Lactel (Box 31)
    - Unisabi (Frolic) (Box 31)
    - Brandt (Box 31)
    - Scott Continental (Le Trèfle) (Box 31)
    - Vittel (Box 31)
    - Merinos (Box 31)
    - Vittel (Box 31)
    - Lamy-Lutti (Box 31)
    - BASF (Box 31)
    - Kelton (Box 31)
    - Promer (Box 31)
    - Kelton (Box 31)
    - Promer (Box 31)
    - Kelton (Box 31)
    - Promer (Box 31)
    - Mobil Oil France (Box 31)
    - Renault 18 (Box 31)
  - 468. 10 Ans de Cinema et de television Publicitaires (2 eme partie). Undated. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 31)
  - 469. Agence McCann Erickson: Citroën. 1985. Umatic. PAL. TRT: 00:45
    - Citroën: Grace Jones (Box 31)
  - 470. POLIO Campaign (Germany). 1983-1985. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 31)
  - 471. McCann Showreel Italy. 1986. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - IMEC: Collezione Estate (Box 31)
    - Aqua Velva (Box 31)
    - GM Automercati Opel O.K. (Box 31)
    - Banco di Roma: Robot (Box 31)
    - Algida Cornetto (Box 31)
    - Jesus Jeans (Box 31)
    - Findus: Sofficini Indianino (Box 31)
    - Algida: Fruit Cocktail Bar (Box 31)
    - G.M. Opel: Operazione Itaca Nettuno (Box 31)
    - Levi's: Promo Belt (Box 31)
    - Coca-Cola: Food (Box 31)
    - Heineken: Taxi (Box 31)
    - China Martini: Ghepardo (Box 31)
    - Sorbetteria Ranieri (Box 31)
    - Intergold (Box 31)
    - Camel: Motorboat (Box 31)
    - Montage (Box 31)
  - 472. La Tua Milano 1979. 1983. Umatic. PAL. TRT: Unknown. (Box 31)
  - 473. Nippon Vicks, Casio, Asahi Beer, NTT, Japan Diners Club, Dai Nippon Jochugiku, Ahsu Seiyaku, Recruit. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Vicks Cough Drops: Secret (Box 31)
    - Vicks Cough Drops: Bug in Throat (Box 31)
    - Casio Data Bank: The Nude President (Box 31)
    - Asahi Beer: Family Can (Box 31)
    - Nippon Telephone & Telecommunication Co. (NTT): Going Home Telephone Call (Box 31)
    - Japan Diners Club (Box 31)
    - Dai Nippon Jochugiku (Kincho Donto): Chappui (Box 31)
    - Ahsu Seiyaku (Dani-Ace): Climbing the Wall (Box 31)
    - Recruit Nagoya Branch: Scribbling (Box 31)
    - Dai Nippon Jochugiku: Kincho Mat (Box 31)
  - 474. Pioneer, Nestlé, Vicks, CCJC/Coke, Toyo Suisan, NTT, National, Suntory, Asahi Beer. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 5:30
    - Pioneer/Private: Akina Nakamori (Box 31)
    - Nestlé Nescafé: Coffee Welcome (Box 31)
    - Vicks cough drops: Ahem Bug (Box 31)
    - CCJC/Coca-Cola: Masquerade (Box 31)
    - CCJC/Cherry Coke: Introduction (Box 31)
    - Toyo Suisan/LL Noodle: Stage in the Rain (Box 31)
    - NTT: Going Home Call (Box 31)
    - National Steam Iron: Hi Press Iron (Box 31)
    - Suntory Toris: Toris Brothers (Box 31)
    - Asahi Beer/Asahi Family Can: The Two Women (Box 31)
  - 475. Dan Rather Newscast on Japanese Advertising. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 31)
    [A short news story on advertising in Japan. Clips from an interview with Barrington Hill of McCann Erickson Japan. Japanese strategy is to capture the viewer's imagination first and present the product later.]
  - 476. Japan--Creative Trends. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 31)
  - 477. McCann-Erickson Hakuhodo/Tokyo: Characteristics of Japanese Advertising Presentation. 1982. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 32)
    - Fuji Film: Photo Stand (Box 32)
    - Asahi Beer: Mini Barrel (Box 32)
    - AGF: Maxim/Kirk Douglas (Box 32)
    - Yamaha: Towny (Box 32)
    - Suntory: Suntory Red/Reiko Ohara (Box 32)
    - Minolta: Yoshiko Miyazaki (Box 32)
    - Coca-Cola: Spring '80 (Box 32)
    - Suntory Brandy: American (Box 32)
    - Kanebo: Soap Beauty (Box 32)
    - Kirin Beer: Summer Festival (Box 32)
    - Parco (Box 32)
    - Nescafé: Paris/Breakfast (Box 32)
    - Nikka Whisky: China (Box 32)
    - Suntory Whisky: China (Box 32)
    - Cemedine: Cemedine for Wood Working (Box 32)
    - Band-Aid: Swimming Club (Box 32)
    - Esso: Space (Box 32)
    - National: Bulb (Box 32)
  - 478. Japanese Advertising. 1981. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Tory's Whiskey: Puppy (Box 32)
    - Unidentified food product: Floating Leaves (Box 32)
    - Lotte candy: Rocking Tree (Box 32)
    - Egg soup: Mountain Climbers (Box 32)
    - Lunch food: Going Swimming (Box 32)
    - Refrigerator: Zoologist Masanori Hala (Box 32)
    - Technics stereo: Headphones/Tear (Box 32)
    - Nissan Silvia Hatchback: Thunderstorm/Ocean Road (Box 32)
    - Esso Uniflo Oil: Space (Box 32)
    - Inoui perfume: Violinists (Box 32)
    - Levi's: Interview in the Movies (Box 32)
  - 479. Japanese Commercials. 1982. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 5:00
    - Dainippon-Jochugiku Pharmaceutical Co.: Kinchol (spray insecticide) (Box 32)
    - Dainippon-Jochugiku Pharmaceutical Co.: Kinchol (spray insecticide) (Box 32)
    - Dainippon-Jochugiku Pharmaceutical Co.: Kinchol Mats (mat-type insecticide) (Box 32)
    - Dainippon-Jochugiku Pharmaceutical Co.: Kinchol Mats (mat-type insecticide) (Box 32)
    - Dainippon-Jochugiku Pharmaceutical Co.: Kinchol Mats (mat-type insecticide) (Box 32)
    - Dainippon-Jochugiku Pharmaceutical Co.: Cockroach S (spray insecticide) (Box 32)
    - Earth Pharmaceutical Co.: Earth Mats F (Box 32)
    - Earth Pharmaceutical Co.: Earth Mats A (Box 32)
    - Taisho Pharmaceutical Co.: Gokiburi Zorro Zorro (Box 32)
    - Kirin Beer: Kirin Metz (Box 32)
    - Tokyo Marine & Fire Insurance Co.: Non-Life Insurance Policy (Box 32)
    - Tokyo Marine & Fire Insurance Co.: Non-Life Insurance Policy (Box 32)
  - 480. McCann Japanese Commercials: Coke, Nescafé, Asahi Beer. 1984. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Pioneer: Vase (Box 32)
    - Nestlé Nescafé: Coffee Story (Box 32)
    - Coca-Cola Japan: '84 Fall and Winter/Cafeteria (Box 32)
    - Asahi Beer/Nama Tokkuri: Pink Racoons (Box 32)
    - Asahi Beer/Nama Tokkuri: Orange Racoons (Box 32)
  - 481. The Japanese Economy Now. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 32)
    [Ultramodern industrial facilities are the best in the world, but they rely heavily on imported energy and raw materials. Their rapid growth has made them #2 in the world, but they cannot keep this up. They have two problems they must solve: a recession at home; and imbalance with trade abroad--far more exports than imports. The rapid growth of teh '70s was very short-lived. Japan must now fit in with a long-term low-growth process.]
  - 482. Doing Business in Japan. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 32)
    [A film made to point out some of the more obvious differences of foreigh business monies like these observed in its direct contact with a Japanese partner.]
  - 483. Decision Making in Japan. Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: 17:00 (Box 32)
    [A look at Japanese culture in modern Japan that quickly absorbs and incorporates other cultures. This makes it difficult to draw cultural conclusions, but this film triew to draw general guidelines of decision-making in Japan by looking at both traditional and more modern culture.]
  - 484. Suzuki Love--Driving Version; Michael Jackson Commercials, Japanese Motorcycle (Japan). Undated. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - Suzuki Love: Michael Jackson/Red Dress (Box 32)
    - Suzuki Love: Michael Jackson/Balcony (Box 32)
    - Suzuki Love: Michael Jackson/Red Scooter (Box 32)
  - 485. Public Advertising in Japan. 1981. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown.
    - World Competition: Runner (Box 32)
    - World Hunger/Food Waste: Egg/Globe (Box 32)
    - Water Conservation: Human Water Faucet (Box 32)
    - Don't Litter: Copycat Kids (Box 32)
    - World Hunger: Needy Faces (Box 32)
    - Blindness: Blind Pretender (Box 32)
    - Wheelchairs: Bike Rack (Box 32)
    - Child Abuse: Machine Gun Mouth (Box 32)
    - Buckle Up: Car Wreck (Box 32)
    - Buckle Up: Car Seat (Box 32)
    - Buckle Up: Ignition Alarm (Box 32)
    - Tokyo Marine and Fire Insurance Co.: Non-Life Insurance Policy (Box 32)
    - Recycle Aluminum: Beer Can (Box 32)
    - Pay Attention to Driving: Behind the Wheel (Box 32)
    - Be Courteous to Pedestrians: Crosswalk (Box 32)
  - 486. McCann Erickson Peru: Machu Picchu, Cocorocos, Pipos, Vainilla, Coca-Cola Saxo, Goodyear Baby. 1987. Umatic. NTSC. TRT: Unknown. (Box 32, Video-cassette RL00863-UM-0001, Digital-materials RL00863-SET-0001, Video-file RL00863-UM-0001.mov)
    - Coca-Cola: Macchu Picchu (Box 32)
    - Cocorocos candy: Cocorocos Is Loco (Box 32)
    - Pipos crackers: Bar Snacks (Box 32)
    - Vainilla cookies: Hands (Box 32)
    - Coca-Cola: Saxo (Box 32)
    - Goodyear: Baby (Box 32)
  - 487. A Tot Spot. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown. (Box 32)
  - 488. Turkey Reel T.V. Commercials. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Demirdöküm Stove (Box 32)
    - Demirdöküm Radiator (Box 32)
    - Samur Carpet (Box 32)
    - Philips Color TV (Box 32)
    - Nestié Milk Chocolate (Box 32)
    - Bio Tursil Detergent (Box 32)
  - 489. Group I--USA: Atlants, Detroit, Los Angeles, Louisville, New York, San Francisco, Seattle, Houston. Undated. Umatic. TRT: Unknown.
    - Amsouth Bank: Model Bank (Box 32)
    - Atlanta Journal & Constitution: Sports (Box 32)
    - Atlanta Journal & Constitution: Business Woman (Box 32)
    - Coke: The Hot Ones Giveaway (Box 32)
    - Coke: Free Glass promo (Box 32)
    - Buick: Wouldn't You (Box 32)
    - Buick Riviera: Touches You (Box 32)
    - Buick Electra: Round the World (Box 32)
    - Buick Le Sabre: Changes (Box 32)
    - Buick Skylark: Working Car (Box 32)
    - Buick Somerset: Challenge (Box 32)
    - Sprite: Swimming (Box 32)
    - Century 21: Rainy (Box 32)
    - El Pollo Loco: Introducing (Box 32)
    - El Pollo Loco: Introducing (Box 32)
    - El Pollo Loco: Introducing (Box 32)
    - Hilton: Ambition (Box 32)
    - Atlanta Airport Hilton: Dog (Box 32)
    - Myrtle Beach Hilton and Golf Club: Tee Time (Box 32)
    - Fountainbleau Hilton Resort: Excitement (Box 32)
    - Humana Women's Hospital: Breast Diagnostic Center (Box 32)
    - Monfried Optical: Look-Alike World (Box 32)
    - HMO Kentucky: Health Care Cost Option 2000 (Box 32)
    - Blue Cross Blue Shield Kentucky: MVP (Box 32)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken: Summer Meal Deal (Box 32)
    - Kentucky Fried Chicken: Home Delivery (Box 32)
    - Alka Seltzer: Three Alarm Chili (Box 32)
    - L'Oreal Visuelle: Coverage (Box 32)
    - Nescafé: The Pleasure of Coffee (Box 32)
    - Sony Trinitron Color TV: Penguin (Box 32)
    - Coca-Cola: King/Queen (Box 32)
    - AT&T Small Business Experts: Competition (Box 32)
    - Milk: Pole Vaulter (Box 32)
    - Del Monte Vegetables: You Work Hard (Box 32)
    - Wells Fargo Bank: Columbia 1848 (Box 32)
    - Ortho Home Pest Insect Control: Computer Bugs (Box 32)
    - Del Monte Light Fruit: Racquetball (Box 32)
    - Dairy Foods--Calcium: Dance Class (Box 32)
    - Dairy Foods--Calcium: Playground (Box 32)
    - Six Flags: Take You Away (Box 32)
    - Texas State Optical: Phone Gossip (Box 32)
    - Texas Instruments TI-5130 calculator: Tax Time (Box 32)